Let's check out these very Joker wrenches and see what makes them a kind of neat little wrench to have in your toolbox.
You have your ratcheting end right here, so all you have to do is just flip it over to reverse directions on that.
You don't actually have a switch or anything. You just flip the wrench. They're pretty much exactly the same on both sides.
The neat part of these, though, is this little plate that they have right here on this end.
So what that does, if you look right in here, you can see it blocks four of these little spots.
So when you turn your bolt or nut or whatever you're backing out or trying to get started is usually where this shines.
You can see it actually sits on there, so the wrench will actually hold your nut or bolt for you.
Usually if you have a nut up in a really tight spot, it can be a real pain.
You end up trying to put your finger behind it, where with this, if you just put it straight in like that, it will go through.
But put it in right there, it will hold it for you while you get it started.
Just a neat little feature.